teachersnotebook.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy

**What This Privacy Policy Covers  **  
This privacy policy covers the use of the web site located at TeachersNotebook.com and the services provided by Teacher's Notebook, LLC. ("Teacher's Notebook"), including how Teacher's Notebook treats personal information that Teacher's Notebook collects and receives. Pursuant to Teacher's Notebook's Terms of Use, you must be 18 years and older to use this site. Therefore, this policy makes no provision for individuals under 18 years old. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Teacher's Notebook does not own or control, or individuals that Teacher's Notebook does not employ or manage.

Effective Date: April 8, 2011

**Information Collection and How it is Used**  
General Information:

  * Teacher's Notebook will not sell or disclose your name or email address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this privacy policy.
  * Your username, Teacher's Notebook ID or alias is displayed throughout Teacher's Notebook (and so available to the public) and is connected to all of your Teacher's Notebook activity. Other people can see your items for sale, store, feedback, ratings and associated comments. 
  * Teacher's Notebook collects personal information when you register to use Teacher's Notebook services or to post content on Teacher's Notebook. At registration you are asked for your email address and certain other optional information.
  * If you would like to obtain a Seller account, Teacher's Notebook will ask for your billing address, phone number, and credit card information.
  * Teacher's Notebook automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request.
  * Teacher's Notebook uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in Teacher's Notebook's user registration databases when you register with Teacher's Notebook. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes.

**Service-related Announcements  **  
Teacher's Notebook will send you a welcome/confirmation email when you sign up for Teacher's Notebook's services. Receipt of this email is required for using Teacher's Notebook's services.  
Teacher's Notebook will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.

You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing support@TeachersNotebook.com from the email address you signed up with.

**Administrative Messages**  
Teacher's Notebook may periodically email you with administrative messages. Teacher's Notebook will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your information may be combined with information Teacher's Notebook collects from other companies and used to improve and personalize services, content and advertising.

  **Cookies**  
We use cookies, web beacons, and related tools from third parties to provide features and services that improve your buying and selling experience. To help protect your privacy, we limit how these tools can be used on Teacher's Notebook.

**How Teacher's Notebook uses cookies and web beacons**  
“Cookies" are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive once you sign out from Teacher's Notebook or close your web browser.

We use cookies to provide features and services, such as:

  * Promoting and enforcing trust and safety
  * Remembering your preferences
  * Presenting information that’s targeted to your interests
  * Measuring the effectiveness of our sites, services, content, and advertising
  * Providing other services and features that are available only through the use of cookies

A “web beacon” is an electronic image placed in the code of a web page. We use web beacons to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one Teacher's Notebook page to another and to improve site performance.

**Cookies or No Cookies**  
We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies. You are always free to decline cookies if your web browser permits. However, if you decline cookies, you may not be able to use certain Teacher's Notebook features, and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

**Use of cookies and web beacons by third parties**  
We may work with other companies who place cookies or web beacons on our websites. These companies help operate our websites and provide you with additional products and services. 

  **Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
When you post a message, your Teacher's Notebook ID or alias is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Teacher's Notebook may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Teacher's Notebook Terms of Use. Teacher's Notebook may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with Teacher's Notebook's Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy, as Teacher's Notebook in Teacher's Notebook's sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, Teacher's Notebook may disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name. Teacher's Notebook may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

Teacher's Notebook is affiliated with a variety of businesses and works closely with them. These businesses may operate stores on the Teacher's Notebook website or sell items to you from the Teacher's Notebook website. Teacher's Notebook may also provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. Due to the nature of Teacher's Notebook's business model, when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, you will share customer information that is related to such transaction with that affiliated business.

Teacher's Notebook employs other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and needs to share your information with them to provide products and services to you. Examples include but are not limited to fulfilling orders, handling billing disputes and collections, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service.

Teacher's Notebook will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when Teacher's Notebook has your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Teacher's Notebook's Terms of Use, as specified in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by law. In some cases, Teacher's Notebook may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Teacher's Notebook will transfer information about you if Teacher's Notebook is acquired by or merged with another company.

As part of the buying and selling process, you may obtain another Teacher's Notebook user's email address, shipping address and/or other information. Pursuant to Teacher's Notebook's Terms of Use, you have a limited license to use this information. This information should only be used for Teacher's Notebook-related communications or for Teacher's Notebook-facilitated transactions. Teacher's Notebook has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without limiting the foregoing, without express consent from the user, you are not licensed to add any Teacher's Notebook user to your email or physical mail list.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and Teacher's Notebook's ability to keep the community free from bad shopkeepers, Teacher's Notebook will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order, legal process, or substantially similar legal procedure, except when Teacher's Notebook believes in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to protect Teacher's Notebook's rights, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or to report suspected illegal activity.

**Teacher's Notebook News or Feedback**  
If you comment on Teacher's Notebook news or leave feedback on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by others or could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Teacher's Notebook is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Third Parties**  
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information Teacher's Notebook collects from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are buyers or sellers on Teacher's Notebook or throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Teacher's Notebook does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. Teacher's Notebook is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the Teacher's Notebook site. Teacher's Notebook encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Editing and Deleting Account Information**  
You can change your Teacher's Notebook Account Information (except your username), at any time. Teacher's Notebook may send you certain communications relating to the Teacher's Notebook service, such as service-related announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your Teacher's Notebook account. You can delete your Teacher's Notebook account by emailing support@TeachersNotebook.com. Please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in Teacher's Notebook's records until no longer deemed needed by Teacher's Notebook .

Teacher's Notebook limits access to personal information about you to employees who Teacher's Notebook believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Teacher's Notebook Account Information is password-protected. If your personally identifiable information changes you may correct or update it by making the change on your Dashboard Page. You may delete or deactivate your account by emailing Customer Support at support@TeachersNotebook.com

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. Your Teacher's Notebook account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Teacher's Notebook follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once Teacher's Notebook receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Teacher's Notebook does its best to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Teacher's Notebook cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on Teacher's Notebook's Web site, you can email Teacher's Notebook at support@TeachersNotebook.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
If the privacy policy is changed, Teacher's Notebook will post changes so that you are aware of those changes. Teacher's Notebook reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If Teacher's Notebook makes material changes to this policy you will be notified here, by email, or other places Teacher's Notebook deems appropriate.

**Questions**  
If you have questions or suggestions you can contact Teacher's Notebook's Support Team via our Help section.
